



- humphreys.geoff@gmail.com
- **(**352) 665 1142
- www.geoffhumphreys.com

# **ABOUT**

I am a community-minded innovator and thought explorer. More than a decade of starting and managing businesses has taught me that working with a team of smart, kind people to create an awesome experience for others is my idea of a good life.

# **SKILLS**

- Ruby on Rails
  MongoDB
- Javascript
- MySql
- HTML/CSS3
- PostgreSql
- Node.is

- Responsive
- Git
- Web Design
- RESTful APIs

## **EXPERIENCE**

## OWNER/OPERATOR

Taradiddle Design Inc | 2015 - Present

- Collaborate with clients on design and construction, and provide guidance on aesthetic and structural factors such as space planning, layout, and budget based on their needs and requests
- Maintain a design library with new products and vendors to meet the needs of varying homes and clientele
- Coordinate directly with industry leaders to deliver superior products to the client

#### STORE OPERATOR

Pop-A-Top | 2013 - 2015

- Designed and opened a corner store in a high traffic downtown which generated \$250,000 in the first year, with continued growth month over month
- Supervised a team of six employees by creating weekly schedules and task lists and developing a framework to maintain regular and honest communication

## OWNER/OPERATOR

Boca Fiestal 2009 - 2013

- Designed, built and managed a restaurant, bar and outdoor event hall with annual revenues of over \$1,000,000 and more than 50 employees
- Developed and operated the online marketing strategy, including all social media accounts and maintenance of the organization website
- Organized and coordinated daily events at the 500 person outdoor concert hall, including live music, art and film exhibits, and events with community leaders and political committees

## **EDUCATION**

## **BACKEND ENGINEERING CERTIFICATE**

The Iron Yard 2017

### ASSOCIATE OF ARTS - AMERICAN HISTORY

Santa Fe College 2015